<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolio on AWS. DevOps. Python.</title><link>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Portfolio on AWS. DevOps. Python.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advertisement Classification Based on Google Inception V3</title><link>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-4/</guid><description>Project Requirements Video ads classification using Google Inception V3 (GCP) Project Details Advertisement classification via python / inception v3 Achieved 87 % accuracy, with the ability to process 100&amp;rsquo;s videos Google inception v3 re-trained as per own requirement Skills: Python, GCP</description></item><item><title>Cryptocurrency Trading Platform - CCTP</title><link>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-1/</guid><description>Project Requirements Design an Intelligent NLP-based high-frequency trading desktop application utilizing Binance API Project Details Fully object-oriented platform with up to 10,000 microtransactions/minute via Binance API Custom algorithm with a 59% profit ratio, utilizing sentiment analysis and technical analysis Sentiment analysis via NLP/N-grams, Technical analysis via SMA/EMA/Bollinger bands Coded in Python, Machine learning model trained via GCP Deployed to windows hosts via docker Skills: Python, GCP, Binance API, NLP, Docker</description></item><item><title>Forrest Brazeal's Cloud Resume Challenge - This website!</title><link>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-2/</guid><description>Project Requirements Design an AWS-based full-stack serverless website - This website!
Project Details HTML, CSS, JavaScript frontend hosted on S3 AWS Serverless Application Model (SAM) (Cloudformation) for Infrastructure as Code DynamoDB, Lambda, and API Gateway for real-time visitor counter Route 53, ACM, and Cloudfront (CDN) for HTTPS/SSL GitHub Actions for CI/CD using the AWS/SAM CLI Skills: AWS, Python, HTML, CSS, JS, SAM, GitHub Actions</description></item><item><title>Logistics Optimization System</title><link>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-5/</guid><description>Project Requirements Logistics system based on graphs to suggest the most optimal path Project Details Architected logistics movement plan based on graph network Intelligent routing for up to 5000 vehicles tested Various land barriers factored in (weighted graphs) Coded in Python with the help of networkx, osmnx, and pandas Output dynamic routes based on a multitude of factors Skills: Python, Pandas, Leaflet JS, OpenStreetMap</description></item><item><title>Signal Analyzer for Forex</title><link>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://jarraroptimized.com/portfolio/project-3/</guid><description>Project Requirements AI-Algorithm trained on computer vision to detect profitable trades
Project Details Technical indicator analysis via computer vision Utilizing a combination of OCR and data feeds, we were able to extract data from a 3rd party API Coded fully in python, deployed to Windows hosts Skills: Python, OCR</description></item></channel></rss>